Guide to the Oliver F. Atkins photograph collection, 1943-1975
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 4: Personal Papers, Exhibit Images, and Nature Photography, 1940s-1974; (5 boxes)
  - Publications, New York Magazine, August 18, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Parade, 1971-1972 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Publications, President Nixon in Europe, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Publications, The Republican, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Awards, Correspondence, Clippings, Press Binder, 1960s-1970s (Oversize 13)
- Series 5: Oversize, 1943-1971; (12 boxes)
  Series 5 contains oversize mat photographs. Subjects include World War II in Europe, the Korean War, and scenes from Africa, India, and the Middle East. Also pictured are American political figures such as Dwight D. Eisenhower, John F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson, and Richard M. Nixon. Other subjects include protests on the National Mall, landmarks in Washington, D.C. and New York City, coal miners, and Fidel Castro.
  - Street strewn with rubble in Florence, Italy, Giotto's Tower and part of the dome of the Duomo can be seen to the far upper right, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
    10 1/4" x 13"
  - Soldiers in military regalia marching along trail over hills, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
    10 1/4" x 13 1/4"
  - Naples, Italy - Red Cross women disembark from troop ship, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 3)
    13" x 10 1/8"
  - Paratroopers drop from planes over farmlands, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
    13" x 10"
  - Italy - American Red Cross Representative with farmer near make-shift bomber base, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 5)
    10 1/4" x 13 1/8"
  - Italy - U.S. jeeps and truck with personnel surveying bombed-out area, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 6)
  - Italy - American Red Cross person with soldier in tent on muddy field with cannon and jeep nearby, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 7)
    9 5/8" x 13 1/8"
  - Naples, Italy - Pile of German aircraft at edge of Capo di Chino airfield, these were strafed and destroyed on the ground, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 8)
  - Italy - American soldiers with barbed wire and equipment, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 9)
    10 1/8'" x 11 1/4"
  - Italy - American soldiers eating rations among ancient temple ruins, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 10)
    13 1/8" x 10 1/4"
  - Red Cross men attending to wounded man on stretcher, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 11)
  - Two soldiers in dug-out on hillside with bazooka, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 12)
    10" x 13"
  - Soldiers resting, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 13)
  - Soldiers building pontoon bridge - "Light machine gun mounted on jeep stands sentry against enemy aerial attack as pontoon bridge is being completed across the River Rapido." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 14)
  - Italy - two Red Cross women serving refreshments to crew of the 155th rifle artillery under camouflage netting, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 15)
  - Scene of four soldiers around sand-bagged bunker, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 16)
  - "Anzio Beachhead - Red Cross Hospital worker Esther Richards in foxhole under her cot. Two hours after this picture was made she was killed by Nazi aerial bombardment." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 17)
  - Red Cross women serving hot coffee and doughnuts to soldiers on a frosty morning, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 18)
  - Three soldiers in shelled building survey the area, 1940s (Oversize 1, Folder 19)
  - Nurse with I-V overhead bending over patient not seen in photograph, 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 1)
  - Nurse with I-V overhead bending over patient not seen in photograph, 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
  - Interior of warehouse with huge numbers of wooden crates marked in Red Cross, 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
  - "Naples, Italy. 1943. During typhus epidemic in this bomb-blast city. Citizens seeking shelter from nightly bombings in caves under the city were liberally sprayed with DDT powder to kill fleas and lice. This was during World War II when the Allies were in the Casino sector." (Newspaper caption), 1944 (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
    two copies; 10 1/4" x 13"
  - "Naples, Italy, 1944 (?). DDT spraying operations in underground caves during typhus epidemic in Naples in World War II. Pictured here under American military supervision Neapolitans were being liberally treated to kill lice and fleas on them. They shelter nightly in the caves because of aerial bombings at night." (Newspaper caption) (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
  - Naples, Italy, 1944 (?). DDT spraying operations in underground caves during typhus epidemic in Naples in World War II. Pictured here under American military supervision a family is being liberally treated to kill lice and fleas on them. This whole family and hundreds of others sought safety in the caves because of aerial bombings at night. (Newspaper caption) (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
  - Street scene in Italy, 1944 (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
  - Sculptors working on statue of men carrying a wounded soldier, two photographs mounted together, 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
    9 3/4" x 13 1/8" and 9 1/2" x 13 1/4"
  - Atomic submarine shown submerging (Ollie Atkins note: Date taken 1955) (Oversize 2, Folder 10)
  - Two unidentified ships in the water, 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 11)
    8 5/8" x 13 1/4"
  - Palermo, Sicily - Italian couple at dinner. "With the front just passed this city an Italian couple enjoy a quiet meal in the ally with the family cat patiently awaiting a scrap." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 12)
  - "Yugoslavian Family" "Bari, Italy--Yugoslavian refugees on fishing boat arriving here from Yugoslavia." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 13)
    13 1/4" by 10 1/4"
  - "Bari, Italy, 1944?" "Yugoslavian refugees pictured in Bari, Italy, during World War II after they had escaped from war-torn Yugoslavia in small fishing vessels. As soon as they were placed in DP camps they were well dusted with DDT powder." (Newspaper caption) (Oversize 2, Folder 14)
  - "Naples, Italy--Night time exposure showing air raid over this allied-held city. The bright wiggly lines are from flares dropped by German aircraft. The dots are Allied flack bursts. The thin lines are tracers from ground machine gun fire. The long streak at upper right of center is the trail of a bright star during the time exposure of about a half-hour." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 15)
    three copies
  - Unidentified farm woman planting potatoes., 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 16)
    13 3/8" x 8 5/8"
  - Florence, Italy - Ponte Vecchio with ruins seen across the River Arno., 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 17)
  - "Berlin--German refugees leaving Berlin and passing the Reichstag as troops take over the city." (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 2, Folder 18)
  - Portrait of General Matthew Ridgeway in field uniform with grenade at shoulder and "Airborne" patch on sleeve, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 1)
    13 1/4" x 10"
  - Three quarter length portrait of General Matthew Ridgeway, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 2)
    13 7/8" x 8 1/2"
  - Bazooka being fired with four servicemen in sandbag lined bunker shutting out noise with hands to ears, one with telephone, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
  - Large groups of soldiers halted on road with one helicopter on ground and another coming in for landing, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
  - Soldier working on machine gun with supply of hand grenades laid out on the ground nearby like eggs in a nest, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
    10 1/8" x 13"
  - Soldier with rifle across lap, eating from can what appears to be beans, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
    12 3/4" x 10"
  - Convoy of military vehicles halted with group of officers in consultation with a group of orientals in their uniform, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
    9" x 13"
  - Two U.S. military pilots with two Korean military pilots are under the nose of a bomber going over map. All are wearing parachutes., 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
  - Soldier moving forward on knees with rifle in hand, hand grenades dangling from shoulder and dog tags and cross on chains around neck, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 9)
  - Three soldiers in field, one with shovel, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 10)
    10" x 12"
  - Soldiers on tank and others lying on stretchers with medicine men in attendance, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 11)
  - Soldiers building bunker by piling up sandbags, others filling bags with sand, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 14)
  - Scene at river with men in the water laying barbed wire, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 15)
    10" x 12 1/2"
  - Soldier smoking cigarette in bunker surrounded by snowy landscape, "Infantry light machine gunner on guard duty during lull in Korean fighting" (Newspaper caption), 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 16)
  - Two soldiers seated and talking to bearded, old Korean man, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 17)
    12 1/2" x 10"
  - Korean woman nattily dressed in military uniform in Korean landscape, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 18)
  - Young Korean boy carrying an enormous load on his back, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 19)
  - Korean uniformed man holding what appears to be a camera, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 20)
    12 1/2" x 9 3/4"
  - Two Koreans seated next to a boat enjoying bowls of rice, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 21)
    11 3/4" x 10"
  - Three Koreans followed by soldier, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 22)
    11 1/4" x 13"
  - General Matthew Ridgway pictured in Korea at the time of United Nations attempt to affect a cease-fire in the area, 1940s (Oversize 3, Folder 23)
  - Franklin Delano Roosevelt in tails assisted by unidentified officer, 1930s-1940s (Oversize 4, Folder 1)
    8 1/4" x 5 1/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower with John Foster Dulles, "President Eisenhower seeing Secretary of State John Foster Dulles off as Dulles left Washington National Airport for Middle East consultations." (Newspaper caption), 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 2)
    13 1/2" x 10"
  - Portrait of Harry S. Truman, 1940s-1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 3)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower with Winston Churchill, "Ike returns to Washington following heart attack - 1954" (Newspaper caption) (Oversize 4, Folder 4)
    7 1/4" x 9 1/2"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at Press Conference in 1955, Forefinger to wrinkled brow, "Let me think now!" (Atkins caption) (Oversize 4, Folder 5)
    13" x 9 1/2"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at Press Conference standing before microphones, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 6)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower animated speaking with microphone before him, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 7)
    13 1/4" x 8 1/8"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower pointing finger at questioner, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 8)
    13 1/4" x 9 3/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower speaking with microphones in front, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 9)
    13" x 9 3/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower in a study of serious contemplation, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 10)
    13 1/4 x 9 3/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower. One large portrait and give small portraits. "Study of President Eisenhower made at his September press conference." (Newspaper caption), 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 11)
    19 1/2" x 9 1/4"; 4 1/4" x 2 3/4"
  - Four studies of Dwight D. Eisenhower, two wearing glasses, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 12)
    10" x 6 3/4"; 9 1/2" x 6 1/2"
  - Six studies of Dwight D. Eisenhower, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 13)
    7" x 4 3/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower with Mamie Eisenhower in back seat of limousine, "Ike returns to Washington following heart attack." (Newspaper caption), 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 14)
    9 1/4" x 13 1/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower with Mamie Eisenhower in back seat of white convertible, President Eisenhower standing and waving to crowds lining street, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 15)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower and Mamie Eisenhower with Governor Thomas E. Dewey and others, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 16)
    8 3/4" x 13 1/8"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower smiling broadly and waving in front of sign which reads in part, "Welcome Ike, Western Governors", a number of unidentified people in the background, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 17)
    20" x 16"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower as spectator, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 18)
    5" x 8"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower as spectator, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 19)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower as spectator, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 20)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Presidential Inauguration, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 21)
    10 5/8" x 13 1/2"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Winston Churchill and Anthony Eden, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 22)
    13" x 10 1/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at work inside airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 23)
    13" x 10 3/8"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Jim Hagarty and several other unidentified persons, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 24)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at desk in Oval Office, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 25)
    10 1/4" x 11 3/4"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower at airport greeting Arabian leaders, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 26)
    10 1/4" 13"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower in open vehicle with a group of unidentified people, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 27)
    10 3/4" x 13"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower addressing a crowd in tent, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 28)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower and Mamie Eisenhower, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 29)
    13" x 8 1/2"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, Sherman Adams and unidentified woman in airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 30)
    9 1/2" x 13"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower working in airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 31)
    9 1/4" x 13"
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower working in airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 32)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower working in airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 33)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, reflective mood in airplane, 1950s (Oversize 4, Folder 34)
  - John F. Kennedy with Ethel and Robert Kennedy looking at newspaper with lead story of his race for the U.S. Senate, 1950s (Oversize 5, Folder 1)
    13 1/8 x 10 1/8"
  - Extreme close-up portrait of John F. Kennedy in three quarter view, 1950s-1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 2)
    17" x 11 5/8"
  - Portrait of John F. Kennedy in rocking chair with reporters and photographers, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 3)
  - Portrait of John F. Kennedy in the Oval Office in the White House working at desk seen through doorway, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 4)
    13 1/4" x 5 5/8"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson sitting on chairs on platform with Kennedy laughing, presumably at Johnson's remarks, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 5)
    13 1/2" x 9"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson sitting on chairs on platform with both men laughing, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 6)
    13" x 8 6/8"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson sitting on chairs on platform with both men laughing, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 7)
    12 1/4" x 8 1/8"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson waving in entrance to building with newsman and others in background, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 8)
    9 1/2" x 13 1/4"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson waving in entrance to building with newsman and others in background, with the two men engaged in serious conversation, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 9)
    10" x 13 1/4"
  - John F. Kennedy and Lyndon B. Johnson with Henry Martin "Scoop" Jackson in animated conversation, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 10)
  - John F. Kennedy, Lyndon B. Johnson, and Henry Martin "Scoop" Jackson seated and engrossed in serious discussion, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 11)
    9" x 13 1/4"
  - Robert F. Kennedy with bull horn speaking to group, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 12)
    10 1/2" x 13 1/2"
  - Presidential caisson carrying body of John F. Kennedy with the U.S. Capitol Building in the background, 1963 (Oversize 5, Folder 13)
    8 3/8" x 13 1/4"
  - Night scene at cemetery for burial of Robert F. Kennedy with his widow Ethel Kennedy in black veil covering face being escorted by Edward Kennedy and other members of the family gathered around, 1968 (Oversize 5, Folder 14)
    8 3/4" x 13 1/4"
  - Night scene at cemetery for burial of Robert F. Kennedy with his widow Ethel Kennedy in black veil covering face being escorted by Edward Kennedy and other members of the family gathered around, closeup, 1968 (Oversize 5, Folder 15)
    15" x 19 3/4"
  - Night scene at cemetery for burial of Robert F. Kennedy with his widow Ethel Kennedy in black veil covering face being escorted by Edward Kennedy and other members of the family gathered around, long view, 1968 (Oversize 5, Folder 16)
    14 1/2" x 15 3/4"
  - Night scene at cemetery for burial of Robert F. Kennedy with his widow Ethel Kennedy in black veil covering face being escorted by Edward Kennedy and other members of the family gathered around, pall bearers called forward, 1968 (Oversize 5, Folder 17)
    14 3/4" x 19 1/4"
  - Night scene at cemetery for burial of Robert F. Kennedy with his widow Ethel Kennedy in black veil covering face being escorted by Edward Kennedy and other members of the family gathered around, 1968 (Oversize 5, Folder 18)
    14" x 17 1/2"
  - John F. Kennedy and Robert F. Kennedy sitting on a sofa, 1960s (Oversize 5, Folder 19)
  - Extreme close-up portrait of Lyndon B. Johnson, appears amused, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 1)
    18" x 14"
  - Pensive portrait of Lyndon B. Johnson, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 2)
    17 5/8" x 11 1/2"
  - Portrait of Lyndon B. Johnson, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 3)
    13 1/2" x 10 3/8"
  - Profile portrait of Lyndon B. Johnson, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 4)
    13 1/4" x 9"
  - Portrait of Lyndon B. Johnson leaning over and laughing, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 5)
    13 1/4" x 8 1/2"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson on horseback with United States helicopter in background, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 6)
    9 1/8" x 13 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and Hubert H. Humphrey on horseback, Humphrey looks apprehensive, United States flag in background at half-mast, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 7)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and Hubert H. Humphrey enjoying plates of barbecued ribs on the President's Texas ranch, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 8)
    12 5/8" x 9 7/8"
  - White limousine with cattle in a field, driver unidentified but probably Lyndon B. Johnson, passenger appears to by Lady Bird Johnson, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 9)
    7 1/8" x 13 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson at podium on his Texas ranch with group of media people, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 10)
    10 1/4" x 13 1/2"
  - Close-up of Lyndon B. Johnson reading at teleprompter, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 11)
    10 3/8" x 12 1/2"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in back of limousine waving to crowd lining street, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 12)
    8 1/8" x 13 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and Lady Bird Johnson portrait at rail fence in front of their Texas ranch house, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 13)
    13 1/4" x 10 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in Oval Office in the White House watching space shot on television with Robert S. McNamara, [Arthur J.] Goldberg and other, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 14)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson on lawn with [Alexander] Haig and others, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 15)
    13 1/8" x 9 1/4"
  - Hubert H. Humphrey and wife Muriel Humphrey sitting on back of convertible with Herbert Humphrey waving to small crowd on sidewalk, Humphrey's drug store in background, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 16)
    9 1/8" x 13 3/4"
  - Scene of Democratic convention, Lyndon B. Johnson running for nomination, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 17)
    8 1/2" x 13 1/2"
  - Young woman in bathing suit seated on donkey with a group of men looking up, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 18)
    9 3/4 x 13 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in hospital bed, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 19)
    9" x 13 1/8"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in hospital bed with Lady Bird Johnson and daughter Lucy looking on, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 20)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson at podium of Democratic convention, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 21)
    8 1/2" x 13"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in crowd of admirers, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 22)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson at official signing ceremony with Hubert H. Humphrey and other looking up, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 23)
    13 1/2" x 9 1/4"
  - Photograph of hands only showing the president at official signing ceremony with souvenir pens in holder in foreground, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 24)
    10 1/8" x 10 1/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson at official signing ceremony tossing last of souvenir pens, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 25)
    9 3/8" x 13"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson with Cabinet during working session, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 26)
    8 1/4" x 13"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson with unidentified man, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 27)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and members of his staff, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 28)
    13 1/4" x 10 1/2"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson with unidentified man, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 29)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in Oval Office, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 30)
    12 7/8" x 8 1/8"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson portrait, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 31)
    12 3/4" x 7 3/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson portrait (wearing hat), 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 32)
    9 3/4" x 9 3/4"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson portrait of upper half of his face with an amused expression in his eyes, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 33)
    10 1/4" x 11 1/2"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and Hubert H. Humphrey on horseback, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 34)
    10 1/4" x 10 3/8"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, Robert S. McNamara, Dean Rusk, and George Bundy, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 35)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson with two White House staff members, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 36)
    10 3/8" x 13"
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and Lady Bird Johnson at rail fence on their Texas ranch, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 37)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson in hospital bed after surgery, 1960s (Oversize 6, Folder 38)
    8 3/4" x 12 3/4"
  - Norman Rockwell, American artist, portrait, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
  - Harold Ickes portrait, Secretary of Interior (1933-1946), 1930s-1940s (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
  - Nelson Rockefeller portrait, Governor of New York, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
    13 1/8 x 10"
  - Nelson Rockefeller portrait with microphone in shirt sleeves, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
    13 1/4" x 7 7/8"
  - Adlai Stevenson in Bloomington, Indiana in coverall watching Charles A. Mercier tossing hay to cattle, February 1949 (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
    10 1/2" x 12 5/8"
  - Robert McNamara inspecting ancient text, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
    10 1/4" x 12 1/4"
  - John L. Lewis portrait, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 7)
    13 1/4" x 10 3/8"
  - Samuel J. Ervin, Jr. portrait, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 8)
  - Samuel J. Ervin, Jr. portrait, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 9)
  - Christian A. Herter portrait, 1959-1960 (Oversize 7, Folder 10)
    13 3/8" x 10 1/2"
  - James Forrestal portrait, 1940s (Oversize 7, Folder 11)
  - James Forrestal portrait, 1940s (Oversize 7, Folder 12)
  - Bernard Baruch portrait, 1940s (Oversize 7, Folder 13)
    13 1/4 x 10 1/4"
  - Unidentified man testifying, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 14)
  - Street scene with crowds lining street and limousine surrounded by what appear to be secret service men and motorcycle police, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 15)
  - James Hagerty speaking to press, 1950s (Oversize 7, Folder 16)
  - Thomas J. Dodd on trial, June 1967 (Oversize 7, Folder 17)
    11 7/8" x 18 3/4"
  - Unidentified hooded person in front of microphone appears to be testifying, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 18)
    12 3/8" x 9 5/8"
  - Unidentified hooded person in front of microphone appears to be testifying, 1960s (Oversize 7, Folder 19)
    9" x 11"
  - Pope Pius XII seated on throne, 1940s-1950s (Oversize 8, Folder 1)
  - Three-quarter portrait of Pipe Pius XII shown blessing, 1940s-1950s (Oversize 8, Folder 2)
  - Portrait of Jawaharlal Nehru of India, 1960s (Oversize 8, Folder 3)
  - Close-up portrait of Fidel Castro, 1950s (Oversize 8, Folder 4)
    13 1/2" x 7 3/4"
  - Fidel Castro highly animated, speaking to group of people, 1950s (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
    13 1/4" x 9 1/2"
  - Fidel Castro highly animated, speaking to group of people, 1950s (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
  - Prophet Jones, bejeweled, seating and waving, "Messiah in Mink", 1955 (Oversize 7, Folder 7)
    13" x 9 1/4"